http://pharmacy.rutgers.edu/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentEMSOPRBHSRutgers HealthRutgersInfo forProspective StudentsIncoming StudentsCurrent StudentsEMSOP 2020 Virtual ConvocationInformation SessionsCOVID19 ResourcesApplyCalendarContact UsDonate
Search
Search:
Hit enter to search or ESC to closeHome » Privacy PolicyWEB PRIVACY POLICYErnest Mario School of Pharmacy (EMSOP) is committed to safe-guarding the privacy and accuracy of your confidential information to the extent possible, subject to provisions of state and federal law. Other than as required by laws guaranteeing public access to certain types of information, or in response to subpoenas or legal instruments that authorize access, personally-identifiable information is not actively shared. We do not re-distribute or sell personal information collected on our web servers. Information CollectedOnline forms may collect information such as name, address, e-mail address, telephone number(s), and/or educational interests. Web servers may collect, temporarily, information such as: Internet Protocol (IP) address of computer being used; web pages requested; referring web page; browser used; date and time, etc.Google AnalyticsErnest Mario School of Pharmacy web sites use Google Analytics, a tool used to understand how visitors interact with the EMSOP web site. Google Analytics uses cookies. Data gathered from Google Analytics is not personally identifiable and is restricted for use by employees of Rutgers University. Google provides visitors with a method to opt-out of Google Analytics.Ernest Mario School of Pharmacy web sites also use Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. This feature approximates website visitor demographics and interests and uses cookies. Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting does not capture personally identifiable information and is restricted for use by employees of Rutgers University. You may opt-out of this feature by visiting Google Ads Settings.Distribution of Collected InformationErnest Mario School of Pharmacy will not disclose, without your consent, personal information collected about you, except for certain explicit circumstances in which disclosure is required by law. EMSOP will not distribute or sell personal information to third-party organizations.Responsibility for Linked-To SitesWhile using a Ernest Mario School of Pharmacy web site, you may see links to web pages of organizations not directly affiliated with Rutgers University. Ernest Mario School of Pharmacy does not control the content or information policies of external organizations. We recommend you review the privacy statements of these organizations.
